RESUME

Archana Moger

Phone: +91-7353095857 E-mail: mogerarchana@gmail.com

About Myself

Motivated and creative individual with 5.2 years of experience in customer service via call chat and email. I have 2 years of experience working in a Fintech company. Well-versed with the processes related to remittance services, credit and debit cards and handling escalation emails, refunds, disputes, cancellations, and other customer queries and issues.

Work Experience

Jan 16 2023- July 2023

Senior Executive Customer Experience- NIUM India Pvt Ltd

- Providing remittance support for International customers through email, chat and calls and have achieved the target set.
- Handling queries related to payments, refund and other account related queries.
- Handling escalation tickets raised to different teams.
- Have received appreciation from customers, and monthly targets achieved consistently.

Jul 2021- Jan 6 2023

Customer Excellence and acting Lead- Zolve Innovations Pvt Ltd (Fintech)

- Handling Chats and escalation emails to address queries regarding payments, disputes, transactions, KYC, On-boarding, account-related issues, and statement-related concerns.
- Working with product, tech, credit, compliance, and risk teams to resolve customer issues. Promoted as Acting lead, taking care of the whole customer support chat team and email team shift-wise by assisting the agents, providing training to new joiners, and assisting them.
- Up skilled to handle fraud dispute cases.

• Handled maximum number of chats and emails and along with achieving the set target each month.

Aug 2019- May 2021

Customer Service Executive L-3 - NoBroker Technologies Solutions Pvt Ltd

- Generating leads to achieve the predetermined revenue. Providing excellent customer service.
- Handling all aspects of customer complaints and disputes and resolving any customer complaints in a friendly, courteous manner.

Mar 2018- Jul 2019

Customer Relationship Officer- Hinduja Global Solutions (Airtel Broadband Process)

- Documenting any major problems customers are facing with the product/service & solving customer queries.
- Calling the customer, troubleshooting the network issue, and resolving. Promoted to handle higher escalation emails such as Appellate and Nodal emails.
- Worked as an SME, handling a team of 12 members. Giving updates each day, helping to achieve the target associated.

Educational Qualification

- MBA (Human Resource) Visveshwaraya Technological University, 64 %
- ➤ BBA, Karnataka University Dharwad, 71%
- ➤ Board of Intermediate Education (10+2), Guru Sudhindra College, Bhatkal, 50%
- > Secondary School Certificate, New English School (Bhatkal), 69%

HOBBIES

Painting, Cooking, Gardening, Trekking, Traveling, and Listening to music.

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to the best of my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Date: Signature/-

Place: Bangalore ARCHANA MOGER